

Thu Hang Le

Graduate Statistician/ Data Analyst

My Contact

Marsfield, NSW 2122



🗹 hanglth@gmail.com



mana-le.com



in linkedin.com/in/hanglth



🦙 github.com/Hana-Le

Education Background

- Macquarie University Masters of Applied Statistics Completed in Dec 2022 **WAM 85**
- University of Queensland Master of Project Management
- Vietnam National University, Hanoi Bachelor of Science

Technical Skills

- R
- SOL
- Tableau
- Excel Data Analysis
- Python
- Data Visualisation
- · Statistical Modeling
- · Data Analysis

Soft Skills

- Skilled in stakeholder partnership management across sectors
- Adaptable to diverse working styles
- Experienced in diverse team collaboration
- Solution-focused and data-driven

About Me

Recent Applied Statistics grad with WAM 85 and passion for data analytics. Skilled in data manipulation and analytics tools such as R, SQL, Tableau, and Excel. Seeking opportunities to apply and enhance skills in data manipulation and employ advanced techniques for analysis and interpretation. With 6+ years of project management experience in UN and NGO settings, including data collection and analysis for proposals, monitoring & evaluation, and decisionmakina.

Professional Experience

Avant Mutual | Data Entry Officer

2022 (casual)

Key responsibilities:

Reviewing, verifying and compiling data in the database system.

Oxfam in Viet Nam | Program Officer

2018 - 2019

Key responsibilities:

Design and implementation management of a series of gender and development projects, delivered in partnership with both nongovernment organisations and government agencies.

International Labour Organization | Project Coordinator

2015 - 2017

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1.5m portfolio of projects aimed at improving labour practices in private sector enterprises in Viet Nam.

Care int. in Viet Nam | Project Manager

2010 - 2014

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1m portfolio of projects aimed at delivering public health interventions for disadvantaged and vulnerable communities.

Achievements

- · Successfully managed all projects in charge, including delivering on time, within budget, and to the agreed quality specifications.
- · Achieved a full scholarship for the master's program at Queensland University.